miller-mccune.com 2013-12-27

# Privacy Statement

****This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, which will always be directly accessible through our website's homepage and other pages across our digital network.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
_Pacific Standard_ and PSmag.com respect each individual's right to personal privacy, and there is no need to identify yourself in order to view anything posted on our site. We do, however, collect information directly from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, including your name and/or e-mail address. But we will collect and use information through our website only in the ways disclosed in this statement.

Like most website operators, PSmag.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that Web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. PSmag.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our website. From time to time, PSmag.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

**AGGREGATED STATISTICS**  
PSmag.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, PSmag.com may monitor the most popular pages on the site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. Automattic may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, PSmag.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described in this policy.

**WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?  
**Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: to improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you); to administer a contest, promotion, survey, or other site feature; and to send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**DO WE USE COOKIES?  
**Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**ADVERTISING  
**Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by PSmag.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to both this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad content network privacy policy.

**DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?  
**We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS  
**Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**CHILDRENS ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**RESPONSIBILITY FOR SECURITY BREACHES**  
Although PSmag.com makes concerted efforts to protect its servers and databases from unauthorized access, we are unable to accept liability for information accessed illegally via our servers, clients, or network. Your personal information is protected by the most advanced security systems available to us. However, no system is entirely secure and, as such, PSmag.com makes no legal guarantees regarding the protection of any data that may reside on our servers.

**PRIVACY STATEMENT CHANGES**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, PSmag.com may change its privacy statement from time to time, and in PSmag.com’s sole discretion. PSmag.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to our privacy statement. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy statement will constitute your acceptance of such change.
